Guide to the T. F. Gilroy Daly Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
T. F. Gilroy Daly papers
1950-1996
1988-1996
MS 1718
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
18
(44 boxes)
The papers consist of correspondence, continuing education course materials, legal pleadings, memoranda, newspaper clippings, photographs, reports, subject files, and writings that document T. F. Gilroy Daly's career as a United States District Court judge. The papers provide a comprehensive overview of Daly's career from his appointment in 1977 until his death in 1996. The materials regarding Daly's service as the chief judge of the United States District Court for the District of Connecticut from 1983 to 1988 are extensive and document the substantial administrative responsibilities of the position.
Daly, T. F. Gilroy, 1931-1996
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Estate of T. F. Gilroy Daly, 1996.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
Thomas Francis Gilroy Daly, known as T. F. Gilroy Daly, was born on February 25, 1931, in New York City. He received his B.A. from Georgetown University in 1952. Daly served in Korea in the U. S. Army Rangers from 1953 to 1955 and attained the rank of first lieutenant. After completion of military service, Daly went to Yale Law School where he obtained his J.D. in 1957 and received the John Fletcher Caskey Prize for outstanding performance in a moot court trial.
After graduation, Daly practiced law in Washington, D.C., for five years. He then served as an assistant United States attorney for the Southern District of New York from 1961 to 1964. Daly practiced law in Connecticut from 1964 to 1977. In addition to his practice, he held several positions in Connecticut government: deputy state attorney general from 1967 to 1971, special assistant to the state attorney general from 1971 to 1975, deputy state treasurer from 1975 to 1976, and state insurance commissioner from 1976 to 1977.
Daly gained prominence in the 1970s for his pivotal role in obtaining freedom for Peter Reilly. In 1974, Reilly, aged eighteen, was convicted of manslaughter in the stabbing death of his mother. The conviction was largely based upon Reilly's confession, which his supporters maintained was the product of police coercion. After his conviction, Reilly's supporters convinced Daly to enter the case and appeal the conviction. It was discovered that the prosecutor, now dead, had not disclosed exculpatory evidence to Reilly's attorney. After a six-week hearing, Reilly was released from prison and the charge was dismissed.
Daly was nominated by President Jimmy Carter to serve as a United States District Court judge for the District of Connecticut in 1977. He served on the Court until his death in 1996. He was chief judge of the District of Connecticut from 1983 to 1988.
T. F. Gilroy Daly died on July 11, 1996, and was survived by his wife, Stuart Stetson Daly, and their four children, Timothy, Loan, Matthew, and Anna.
Scope and Contents
The papers consist of correspondence, continuing education course materials, legal pleadings, memoranda, newspaper clippings, photographs, reports, subject files, and writings that document T. F. Gilroy Daly's career as a United States District Court judge. The papers provide a comprehensive overview of Daly's career from his appointment in 1977 until his death in 1996. The materials regarding Daly's service as the chief judge of the United States District Court for the District of Connecticut from 1983 to 1988 are extensive and document the substantial administrative responsibilities of the position.
There are no materials relating to the Peter Reilly court case.
The T. F. Gilroy Daly Papers were processed as a collaborative effort between Manuscripts and Archives and the Yale Law School to document the careers and accomplishments of Law School faculty and alumni.
Arrangement
Arranged in two series: I. Judicial Agencies and Activities, 1966-1996. II. Professional Organizations and Topical Files, 1950-1996.
Civil rights -- United States; Criminal procedure; Judges -- Connecticut; Judicial opinions -- United States; Daly, T. F. Gilroy, 1931-1996; United States. District Court (Connecticut); Yale Law School
- Judicial Agencies and Activities, 1966-1996; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes correspondence, memoranda, newspaper clippings, photographs, reports and other materials created or collected by T. F. Gilroy Daly and relating to various judicial agencies, organizations, and individuals. The majority pertain to federal judicial activities, particularly from administrative agencies such as the Administrative Office of the United States Courts (AOUSC) and from individuals and departments within the Connecticut federal court system. Daly's original filing system, in which materials were filed by the name of the organization, office, or topic, has largely been retained.
  Significant amounts of material document the response of the federal judiciary to crises involving class action suits, alternative dispute resolution methods, criminal sentencing, and increasing number of civil and criminal cases. Also illustrated in the Connecticut District Court files are the wide-ranging administrative responsibilities that Daly had, in addition to his regular caseload, when he served as chief district court judge between 1983 and 1988.
  Correspondence with other district court judges and court officials is largely routine. Congressional correspondence is dominated by repeated requests for additional federal judges for Connecticut and responses by the judiciary to legislative proposals. General correspondence is also largely routine and includes notes and invitations to and from various judicial and political officeholders and letters from the public commenting upon Daly's decisions. Correspondence from prisoners generally includes requests for assistance in obtaining new hearings or trials, improved prison facilities, transfers to other locations, or relief from alleged abuse by prison staff. Also noteworthy are letters, newspaper clippings, and other items exchanged between Daly and his law clerks after the completion of their clerkships.
  - Administrative Office of the United States Courts (AOUSC)
    - General, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Assistant director of administration (Raymond A. Karam), 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Director (Ralph Mecham), 1985-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Judges' Office Automation Training Program, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - "Notorious Trial Checklist", 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Space and facilities branch (Robert F. Baldesari), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Attorney General of the State of Connecticut, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Commemorative dinners, 1981-1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Connecticut state courts, 1988-1996 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  - Connecticut state officials, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence
    - Congress
      - House of Representatives
        - DeLauro, Rosa L., 1990-1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
        - Franks, Gary A., 1991-1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        - Gejdenson, Sam, 1983-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        - Johnson, Nancy L., 1983-1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        - Kennelly, Barbara B., 1983-1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - McKinney, Stewart B., 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
        - Morrison, Bruce A., 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
        - Rowland, John G., 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
        - Shays, Christopher, 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Legislation
        - Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA), 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - General judicial issues, 1984-1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        - Senior judges-Social Security, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        - Violent Crime Control and Law Enforcement Act, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Senate
        - Biden, Joseph R., Jr., 1987-1995 (Box 2, Folder 25)
        - Dodd, Christopher J., 1983-1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
        - Grassley, Charles E., 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 27)
        - Lieberman, Joseph I., 1983-1995 (Box 2, Folder 28)
        - Weicker, Lowell P., Jr., 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - General
      - A-Z, 1983-1996 (Box 3, Folder 30-34)
      - Martin-Trigona, Anthony, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Sullivan, Allen, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Twardy, Stanley (job for Matthew Daly), 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Prisoner
      - General, 1989-1996 (Box 3, Folder 38-41)
      - Additional material (Box 4, Folder 42-43)
      - Ackerman, Matthew, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Copley, Craig, 1973-1995 (Box 4, Folder 45-46)
      - Durrani, Arif, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 47-48)
      - Thurston, Michael E., 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Criminal Justice Act (CJA), 1992-1996 (Box 5, Folder 50-54)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1991-1996 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Federal Bureau of Prisons-prisoner placement, 1989-1995 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Federal Public Defender, 1991-1996 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - General Services Administration, 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Judicial Council of the Second Circuit-Circuit executive, 1983-1996 (Box 5, Folder 59-60)
  - Judges
    - "All District Court judges" memoranda from Daly as chief judge, 1983-1989 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Arterton, Janet Bond, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Blumenfeld, M. Joseph, 1981-1989 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Burns, Ellen Bree, 1984-1996 (Box 6, Folder 64-73)
      - Additional material (Box 7, Folder 74-78)
    - Cabranes, Jose A., 1979-1996 (Box 7, Folder 79-88)
      - Additional material (Box 8, Folder 89-99)
      - Additional material (Box 9, Folder 100-107)
    - Calabresi, Guido, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 108-109)
    - Chatigny, Robert N., 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 110-112)
    - Clarie, T. Emmet, 1978-1988, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 113-127)
    - Covello, Alfred V., 1992-1996 (Box 10, Folder 128-132)
    - Dabrowski, Albert S., 1993-1996 (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - Dorsey, Peter C., 1984-1996 (Box 10, Folder 134-136)
      - Additional material (Box 11, Folder 137-150)
    - Eginton, Warren W., 1980, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 151-165)
    - Feinberg, Wilfred, 1980-1988 (Box 12, Folder 166)
    - Goettel, Gerard L., 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 167)
    - Kaufman, Irving R., 1978-1982 (Box 13, Folder 168)
    - Knapp, Whitman, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 169)
    - Meskill, Thomas J., 1992-1996 (Box 13, Folder 170)
    - Murphy, Thomas F., 1980-1993 (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - Nevas, Alan H., 1985-1996 (Box 13, Folder 172-183)
    - Newman, Jon O., 1982-1996 (Box 13, Folder 184)
    - Oakes, James L., 1988-1992 (Box 13, Folder 185)
    - Peters, Ellen A., 1984-1988 (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Shiff, Alan H. W., 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 187)
    - Speziale, John A., 1983-1985 (Box 14, Folder 188)
    - Squatrito, Dominic J., 1994-1996 (Box 14, Folder 189)
    - Thompson, Alvin W., 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 190)
    - Timbers, William H., 1966-1992 (Box 14, Folder 191)
    - Winter, Ralph K., 1983-1985 (Box 14, Folder 192)
    - Zampano, Robert C., 1980-1995 (Box 14, Folder 193-207)
  - Judges outside of District Court-Connecticut, 1985-1996 (Box 14, Folder 208-210)
    - Additional material (Box 15, Folder 211-222)
  - Law clerks
    - Bailey, Barbara, 1983-1996 (Box 16, Folder 223)
    - Blumenthal, Jeffrey, 1984-1996 (Box 16, Folder 224)
    - Bryce, Phil, 1977-1985 (Box 16, Folder 225)
    - Cahill, Lisa, 1989-1996 (Box 16, Folder 226)
    - Carta, Mark, 1976-1995 (Box 16, Folder 227)
    - Feinberg, Andy, 1987-1993 (Box 16, Folder 228)
    - Filan, James K., Jr., 1992-1996 (Box 16, Folder 229)
    - Flynn, Kathleen, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 230)
    - Garrity-Rokous, E. Gates, 1991-1996 (Box 16, Folder 231)
    - Kelley, David, 1985-1995 (Box 16, Folder 232)
    - Kohler, Mark, 1986-1993 (Box 16, Folder 233)
    - Krask, Robert, 1987-1992 (Box 16, Folder 234)
    - Lawton, Shan, 1978-1992 (Box 16, Folder 235)
    - Luby, Thomas, 1977-1996 (Box 16, Folder 236)
    - Manning, Stephen, 1981-1996 (Box 16, Folder 237)
    - McGowan, Peter, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 237A)
    - Nemiroff, Andrew, 1978-1991 (Box 17, Folder 238)
    - O'Shea, Ann, 1980-1995 (Box 17, Folder 239)
    - Paseltiner, Philip, 1990-1996 (Box 17, Folder 240)
    - Pavlis, Alfred, 1982-1995 (Box 17, Folder 241)
    - Perry, Scott, 1993-1996 (Box 17, Folder 242)
    - Rosenblum, Lisa, 1977-1995 (Box 17, Folder 243)
    - Stone, Kathleen, 1979-1993 (Box 17, Folder 244)
    - Van Hulst, Josh, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 245)
    - Williams, Stephanie, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 246)
  - Law clerks, list of, 1980-1995 (Box 17, Folder 247)
  - Law clerks, selection process for, 1976-1994 (Box 17, Folder 248)
  - Law clerks' dinner, 1990-1994 (Box 17, Folder 249)
  - Law clerks' party photographs, undated (Box 17, Folder 250)
  - Law interns, 1979-1996 (Box 18, Folder 251-254)
  - Magistrates
    - Applications, 1984-1996 (Box 18, Folder 255-257)
      - Additional material (Box 19, Folder 258-261)
    - Eagan, F. Owen, 1983-1996 (Box 19, Folder 262-272)
    - Fitzsimmons, Holly B., 1993-1996 (Box 19, Folder 273)
    - Latimer, Arthur H., 1983-1994 (Box 20, Folder 274-275)
    - Margolis, Joan G., 1985-1996 (Box 20, Folder 276-277)
    - Martinez, Donna F., 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 278)
    - Smith, Thomas P., 1981-1996 (Box 20, Folder 279-280)
  - Management assistance review report, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 281)
  - Office staff memoranda, 1986-1996 (Box 20, Folder 282)
  - U. S. Attorney's office
    - General, 1980-1996 (Box 20, Folder 283-284)
      - Additional material (Box 21, Folder 285-290)
    - Durham, John H., 1990-1995 (Box 21, Folder 291)
  - United States Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit-Daly sitting by designation, 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 292)
  - United States Department of Justice, 1990-1995 (Box 21, Folder 293)
  - United States District Court for the District of Connecticut
    - Audit, 1983-1994 (Box 21, Folder 294-295)
    - Bankruptcy Court, 1987-1996 (Box 22, Folder 296)
    - Budget, 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 297)
    - Case distribution, 1987-1996 (Box 22, Folder 298-301)
    - Civil Justice Reform Act (CJRA), 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 302-304)
    - Clerk of Court
      - Administrative Assistant (Lee Masters), 1986-1996 (Box 22, Folder 305)
      - Chief deputy clerk (Victoria Dalton), 1984-1996 (Box 23, Folder 306-307)
      - Clerk
        - Applications, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 308-309)
        - Markowski, Sylvester A., 1979-1984 (Box 23, Folder 310)
        - Rowe, Kevin F.
          - General, 1982-1996 (Box 23, Folder 311-313)
            - Additional material (Box 24, Folder 314-321)
            - Additional material (Box 25, Folder 322-324)
          - Performance synopsis by Daly, undated (Box 25, Folder 325)
    - Complaints relating to Daly's judicial activities
      - In re charge of judicial misconduct (William M. Laviano, complainant), 1994 (Box 25, Folder 326)
      - Malachowski v. Lambert, et al., 1990-1993 (Box 25, Folder 327)
      - McCarthy, John J., 1992-1995 (Box 25, Folder 328-329)
      - Tosado v. Daly, 1986-1992 (Box 25, Folder 330)
      - Tsimbidaros v. U. S. Dept. of Justice et. al., 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 331)
    - Computer automation (Lori Inferrera), 1991-1996 (Box 26, Folder 332-334)
    - Court reporters, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 335)
    - Courthouses
      - Bridgeport
        - Clerk's office memoranda, 1985-1996 (Box 26, Folder 336-337)
        - Courthouse annex construction, 1985-1994 (Box 26, Folder 338-340)
      - Hartford
        - Clerk's office memoranda, 1984-1994 (Box 26, Folder 341)
        - Courthouse space renovation, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 342)
        - Deputy in charge selection, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 343)
      - New Haven
        - Clerk's office memoranda, 1987-1995 (Box 27, Folder 344)
        - Courthouse re-dedication ceremony 1985, 1970-1985 (Box 27, Folder 345)
        - Courthouse space renovation, 1988-1995 (Box 27, Folder 346)
      - New London space expansion, 1981-1987 (Box 27, Folder 347)
      - Waterbury
        - Clerk's office memoranda, 1985-1995 (Box 27, Folder 348-351)
        - Courthouse space renovation, 1993-1996 (Box 27, Folder 352-353)
          - Additional material (Box 28, Folder 354-355)
    - Grand jury, 1983-1996 (Box 28, Folder 356-358)
    - Intercepted communication reports, 1984-1993 (Box 28, Folder 359)
    - Judgeships
      - General, 1984-1994 (Box 28, Folder 360-361)
      - Sue L. Wise application, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 362)
    - Jury-general, 1987-1993 (Box 28, Folder 363)
    - Jury pool, 1984-1996 (Box 29, Folder 364-370)
    - Jury questionnaires-gender, racial, ethnic, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 371)
    - Jury voir dire questionnaires, 1986-1996 (Box 30, Folder 372)
    - Library, 1988-1996 (Box 30, Folder 373)
    - Probation office (Maria McBride), 1990-1993 (Box 30, Folder 374-379)
    - Secretary (Bruce Likens), 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 380)
    - Security, 1987-1991 (Box 30, Folder 381)
    - Staff attorney (pro se law clerk), 1991-1996 (Box 31, Folder 382-385)
    - Visiting judge's program, 1983-1996 (Box 31, Folder 386-392)
      - Additional material (Box 32, Folder 393-396)
  - United States Foreign Intelligence Act Court of Review (Daly application), 1996 (Box 32, Folder 397)
  - United States Marshal
    - Mangini, Pasquale (Pat), 1987-1991 (Box 32, Folder 398)
    - Security, 1983-1996 (Box 32, Folder 399-403)
  - United States Sentencing Commission, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 404)
  - United States Supreme Court Chief Justice, 1982-1994 (Box 32, Folder 405)
- Professional Organizations and Topical Files, 1950-1996; Series II
  This series includes correspondence, continuing education course materials, newspaper clippings, and other written materials from professional organizations that T. F. Gilroy Daly was a member of, or subject files that he created. Daly was an active member of several federal and state professional organizations and received information from others as a member of the judiciary. Arranged alphabetically by topic or organization name. The majority of the materials in this series relate to activities of the federal and Connecticut bar.
  Topical files consist largely of articles, surveys, and course materials relating to specific legal topics such as class action suits. Also included are several files of speeches that Daly gave at professional meetings and community events.
  - Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome (AIDS), 1987-1991 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Alternative dispute resolution (ADR)
    - General, 1991-1995 (Box 33, Folder 2-4)
    - STA-FED ADR, Inc., 1993-1996 (Box 33, Folder 5-7)
      - Additional material (Box 34, Folder 8-9)
  - American Bar Association (ABA), 1990-1996 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - American Bar Foundation Fellows, 1987-1996 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - American Judicature Society-Edward J. Devitt Award, 1993-1995 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Bar associations-local invitations, 1991-1996 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Connecticut Bar Association
    - General, 1982-1996 (Box 34, Folder 14-15)
    - Arthur Miller Award, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Federal Practice Section, 1990-1996 (Box 35, Folder 17-19)
    - Senior Section, 1992-1996 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Connecticut Bar Foundation, 1994-1996 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Connecticut Criminal Defense Lawyers Association, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Connecticut Judges Association, 1985-1989 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Connecticut Trial Lawyers Association, 1992-1996 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Criminal rules and practice, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Father Panik Village, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Federal Bar Council, 1992-1996 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Additional material (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Federal Bar Foundation, 1991-1995 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Federal Judges Association, 1989-1996 (Box 36, Folder 30-31)
  - Federal Judicial Center
    - General, 1989-1996 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Director search, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Federal Rules of Civil Procedure
    - Federal rules, 1993-1996 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Local rules, 1991-1996 (Box 36, Folder 35-36)
      - Additional material (Box 37, Folder 37-39)
  - Georgetown University, 1990-1996 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - International Institute of Connecticut, Inc., 1982-1996 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Judicial Conference of the Second Circuit, 1988-1996 (Box 37, Folder 42-45)
    - Additional material (Box 38, Folder 46-48)
  - Judicial Conference of the United States, 1988-1996 (Box 38, Folder 49-54)
    - Additional material (Box 39, Folder 55-59)
  - Marriage solemnization, 1977-1985 (Box 39, Folder 60)
  - Mock trial- United States Department of Justice, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 61-62)
  - Moot court competitions, 1989-1995 (Box 39, Folder 63)
  - Morgenthau (Robert M.) Association, 1984-1995 (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Multi-district litigation (class action suit), 1988-1996 (Box 40, Folder 65-69)
  - Naturalization ceremony sessions, 1993-1995 (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - New York State Bar Association, 1981-1996 (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - Photography and recording in court facilities, prohibition of, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - Plea agreements, 1994-1996 (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - Pro bono panel, 1990-1995 (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - Professional organizations-invitations, 1987-1996 (Box 40, Folder 75)
    - Additional material (Box 41, Folder 76-77)
  - Quinnipiac College School of Law, 1994-1996 (Box 41, Folder 78)
  - Red Mass-guild of Catholic lawyers, 1991-1995 (Box 41, Folder 79)
  - Retreat for U. S. District Court- Connecticut judges, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 80)
  - Salary-locality pay adjustment, 1991-1995 (Box 41, Folder 81)
  - Sealing court documents, 1986-1995 (Box 41, Folder 82)
  - Seminars and workshops
    - General, 1984, 1994-1996 (Box 41, Folder 83-84)
    - George Mason University-Law & Economic Center- Institutes for Federal Judges, 1989-1995 (Box 41, Folder 85)
  - Simpson, Thacher & Bartlett, 1984-1996 (Box 42, Folder 86)
  - Special master [court-appointed arbitrator], 1985-1995 (Box 42, Folder 87)
  - Speeches
    - Background materials, 1950-1993 (Box 42, Folder 88-90)
    - Index to speeches, [1996] (Box 42, Folder 91)
    - Speeches, 1973-1996 (Box 42, Folder 92-94)
      - Additional material (Box 43, Folder 95-96)
  - State police litigation (barracks telephone call recording), 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 97)
  - Surveys and questionnaires, 1983-1996 (Box 43, Folder 98-99)
  - United States Attorney's Office for the Southern District of New York, 1989-1994 (Box 43, Folder 100)
  - United States Supreme Court Historical Society, 1990-1996 (Box 43, Folder 101)
  - United Way, 1994-1995 (Box 43, Folder 102)
  - University of Bridgeport, 1984-1993 (Box 43, Folder 103)
  - University of Connecticut, 1984-1996 (Box 43, Folder 104)
  - Wells Fargo bank robbery, Hartford, Conn. news clippings (Los Macheteros), 1986-1992 (Box 43, Folder 105)
    - Additional material (Box 44, Folder 106)
  - West Publishing Company, 1978-1996 (Box 44, Folder 107)
  - Yale Law School, 1991-1996 (Box 44, Folder 108)